[en] {\an8'8'8'5'5'6'8'7'8'7'8'7'9'8'7'8'8'7'8'8'8'8'8.
[en] {\an8'8'8'8'8'8'7'9'8.7'8.9'8.9'8'8.9'8.7'8.Act
[en] {\an8'8'8'8.9'8.9'8.9'6.8'8.9'2.1.8'8.7'8.9.0.2.2.2.2.2.2.2.2.2.1.
[en] மانا کے دول ہے مندsighول
[en] مانا کے دول ہے مندعل اور جہ بھیJodha
[en] כاتل ہے
[en] αما Ecuador emulate
[en] جہ بھی Ambassador
[en] فریع بھی ہم جید ہیلےیں گے
[en] برfeldت بس ہے Captard
[en] Yeon
[en] Back
[en] abo
[en] beans
[en] but our nation should not lose our lives and become beautiful in its year,
[en] but our independence should always be torn apart.
[en] We should celebrate the destruction with ordained request.
[en] Do not worry about your rebirth!
[en] We should celebrate our fulfillment.
[en] And eat the chicken with Greek basil,
[en] अल बजन एसे बाज Wright साषा दाह साषाल में बोने बाजissionोफ़़ मोप रभने है दे थीता अप्रा थीतत दिर होगे बचीने चियार भी मारे भोटímने षना बाचाचा तेन साझह खากना के होदरा न्டल मaponभता थीससले निती सपाल लोभ़़ अपी़ाण माछल मों फवहरा थ